A Guide to the Cartoons by Art Wood, 1952-1959, n.d.
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- ONE PICTURE THAT HASN'T BEEN ALTERED 1954 MAY 01
  World opinion of McCarthy, Joseph
- HERE, THERE AND EVERYWHERE! 1954 MAY 03
  [John Foste]r Dulles, John F. was here
- IT'S SHRUNK! 1954 MAY 04
  United Action policy Allies Geneva laundry Dulles, John F.
- CAN'T YOU SPEED IT UP A BIT? 1954 MAY 05
  Congress McCarthy, Joseph hearings...
- BLOOD ON THE MOON 1954 MAY 06
  Dien Bien Phu Indo-china
- LOOKING FOR A WAY OUT 1954 MAY 11
  the West Indo-chinaese maze
- OUT OF THE ASHES? 1954 MAY 12
  SouthEast Asia Treay Organization (SEATO) Indo-china Dien Bien Phu
- IT'S SLEEPY TIME DOWN SOUTH 1954 MAY 13
  1954 Elections Richmond City Council race
- NO END IN SIGHT 1954 MAY 14
  McCarthy, Joseph hearings John Q
- TWO SIDES TO THE ISSUE 1954 MAY 15
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. Dulles, John F. Indo-china ... dominoes
- AUTO INSPECTION 1954 MAY 17
  United States constitution tightening Supreme Court
- THE SPIRIT OF '54 1954 MAY 18
  Supreme Court rules against desegregation
- LET'S GET TO THE BOTTOM OF IT! 1954 MAY 21
  McCarthy, Joseph hearings Congress
- IT LOOKS A LITTLE RED DOWN THERE! 1954 MAY 22
  United States Communists (Reds) in Guatemala
- AND I UNDERSTAND THEY DRAFT MEN OVER THERE 1954 MAY 25
  France ench plan
- SAY, I'VE GOT AN IDEA 1954 MAY 26
  Immaterial charges... McCarthy, Joseph hearings
- BITTER FRUIT 1954 MAY 27
  The Americas Guatemala
- THE HANDWRITING ON THE WALL 1954 MAY 31
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. McCarthy, Joseph responsibility
- FAMILY PORTRAIT 1954 JUN 02
  Communists (Reds) stalling at UN United NationsAtomic bombs plan Austria
- NOT MUCH TO STAND ON 1954 JUN 04
  Political Parties Republican (GOP) Hopes for party unity McCarthy, Joseph
- GRADUATION BANQUET 1954 JUN 05
  The problems of the world
- THEY ALL SEEM TO FALL! 1954 JUN 15
  Laniel government France
- WILTED 1954 JUN 17
  Communists (Reds) political heat Korean peace hopes Geneva
- WHERE THERE'S SMOKE-THERE'S FIRE 1954 JUN 18
  Churchill, Sir Winston trip to the United States
- WHAT'S IT ALL ADD UP TO? 1954 JUN 19
  McCarthy, Joseph hearings days words pages
- FROM OUT OF THE PAST 1954 JUN 22
  Monroe Doctrine Lodge, Henry C. stay out of hemisphere
- IT DOESN'T SEEM TO DO MUCH GOOD! 1954 JUN 23
  farmers Corn surplus... govt. control
- BANANA SPLIT 1954 JUN 24
  Anti-Communists (Reds) s uprising in Guatemala Pro Communists (Reds)s
- PLENTY TO BE IRONED OUT 1954 JUN 26
  misunderstandings Eisenhower, Dwight D.- Churchill, Sir Winston confer.
- WHO? ME? 1954 JUN 28
  Mendes Help France fight United States citizen
- GO 'WAY BOY - YOU BOTHER ME! 1954 JUL 01
  $200 taxes exemption deficit budget Political Parties Democrats (Dems)
- UNFORTUNATELY, BOB, A MAN IS KNOWN BY HIS FRIENDS 1954 JUL 02
  Oppenheimer
- VICTORY GARDEN 1954 JUL 05
  Political Parties Republican (GOP) St. Lawrence Seaway Taxes bill trade act appropriations
- ROOSTING 1954 JUL 07
  Problem of admitting Red China United Nations
- BETWEEN THE DEVIL AND THE EDC 1954 JUL 09
  Threat of a Germany army France
- SPLIT PERSONALITY 1954 JUL 10
  United Nations - China Knowland Dulles, John F. Political Parties Republican (GOP)
- HEADS I WIN - TAILS YOU LOSE 1954 JUL 11
  McCarthy, Joseph problem
- THERE ARE A LOT MORE OF US THAN THERE ARE OF HIM 1954 JUL 12
  Congress farmers
- PUTTING THEIR HEADS TOGETHER 1954 JUL 13
  Britain France China Geneva talks
- NEITHER SNOW NOR RAIN... 1954 JUL 14
  Congress United States Postal Service postal pay raise
- MAGNIFYING THE PROBLEM 1954 JUL 15
  Worst drought in 20 years public forests
- TURNING ON THE LIGHT AGAIN 1954 JUL 16
  Private enterprise Eisenhower, Dwight D. Tennessee Valley Authority (TVA)
- MARK UP 1954 JUL 19
  Peace in Indo-china Vietnam Russia USSR
- CAVE-IN 1954 JUL 20
  mine closed for lack of business high prices of coal
- MADE IT [alternate: OOPS!] 1954 JUL 21
  Deadline Mendes France
- NOT MUCH HELP NOW 1954 JUL 23
  Plans for a SE Asia defense pact SouthEast Asia Treaty Organization (SEATO) Vietnam
- DIVIDE AND CONQUER 1954 JUL 24
  Southeast Asia Indo-china
- HITTING THE BOTTLE 1954 JUL 24
  Action to give govtTennessee Valley Authority (TVA) right to produce power
- HOT SEAT 1954 JUL 28
  Virginia Political parties Republican (GOP) senate candidate
- CONFUCIUS SAY PICTURE WORTH TEN THOUSAND WORDS 1954 JUL 29
  2 red planes Communists (Reds) Mao Tse-tung
- HICKORY, DICKORY, DOCK 1954 JUL 30
  trade, not foreign aid Political Parties Republican (GOP) Swiss watch tariffs
- THE SUN NEVER SETS ON THE BRITISH EMPIRE 1954 JUL 31
  Nationalism Britain
- REALLY ROLLING 1954 AUG 01
  Eisenhower, Dwight D., program obstruction and delays
- HORNS OF THE DILEMMA 1954 AUG 03
  Congress McCarthy, Joseph censure move
- AND NOW FOR THE NEWS OF THE NEW COMMITTEE INVESTIGATION OF McCARTHY 1954 AUG 06
  Congress McCarthy, Joseph
- PAINTING A TRUE PICTURE 1954 AUG 07
  American patriot Gen. G Marshall, George Eisenhower, Dwight D.
- QUOTH THE RAVEN: NEVERMORE 1954 AUG 09
  Byrd, Harry F., Sr.'s temporary debt budget hike plan
- THE DESERT SONG 1954 AUG 10
  Nationalism uprisings Morocco
- WHOOPEE-E-E 1954 AUG 12
  Political parties Republican (GOP) sliding scale farmers victory
- NO WAY TO GET RID OF HIM 1954 AUG 14
  Senate bill to outlaw Communists (Reds) Party
- WITH ONE VOICE 1954 AUG 17
  Peace ful coexistence Threat on Formosa Mao Tse-tung
- HONOR GUEST 1954 AUG 18
  Attlee visit Mao Tse-tung Malenkov Communists (Reds) Hot Propaganda
- EXECUTIVE SUITE 1954 AUG 20
  Office of the "No Comment" governor of Virginia Governor
- UNIFORM OF THE DAY 1954 AUG 21
  I will vote for any anti- communists (Reds) hasty bill
- COMFY? 1954 AUG 23
  French opposition Mendes France EDC
- LAST WILL AND TESTAMENT 1954 AUG 25
  To the wrath...my death G Vargas Brazil
- ROLES REVERSED 1954 AUG 26
  It's time for a change! You never had it so good
- THE PIED PIPER 1954 AUG 27
  Trade music England, France Malenkov
- HIGH AND DRY 1954 AUG 31
  EDC ebbing French enthusiasm France
- DOWN THE DRAIN 1954 SEP 13
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. the preventive war idea
- I'M BEING FOLLOWED [1954 SEP]
  Tobacco Festival weekend Virginia State Fair
- HOW'S THAT AGAIN? 1954 OCT
  Unemployment Feb 1950 Oct 1954 HST Truman, Harry
- DOUBLE FEATURE 1954 NOV 17
  Mosque now playing the commission listens Gray
- WE ARE GATHERED HERE TODAY 1954 NOV 22
  United States Supreme court 5th United States Constitution amendment ...
- CHRONIC OFFENDER 1954 DEC 03
  Virginia absent voter law Court
- PLENTY TO BE THANKFUL FOR 1954 DEC 25
  The 1st year in 20 with no hot war
- STAMPING IT OUT 1954
  TB Greetings Tuberculosis National Tuberculosis Association (NTA) United States
- MOLASSES IN JANUARY 1955 JAN
  Eisenhower Dwight D.'s 1952 promise to balance budget
- HOLSTER 1955 JUN 18
  Revolt Argentina
- HABIT-FORMING 1955 JUL 04
  1-year extension Congress debt budget ceiling
- FACING ANOTHER SUMMIT 1955 JUL 05
  continued high govt expenses promise budget Eisenhower, Dwight D.
- GETTING DOWN TO EARTH 1955 JUL 07
  "Above it all" campaigning Elections for Virginia General Assembly
- TRAIN OF THOUGHT 1955 JUL 08
  Legislation to be completed Congress railroad
- GOING ALONG FOR THE RIDE 1955 JUL 09
  Overoptimism about conference Geneva Big 4 conference
- EVERYONE'S GOING TO THE MOUNTAINS THIS YEAR 1955 JUL 28
  China United States -Peiping Big 4 conference
- HOT ON HIS TAIL 1955 JUL 29
  Talbott issue
- ROAD SIGN 1955 JUL 30
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. highways plan dead end Congress House
- THE LATEST MODEL 1955 AUG 06
  Approved plan for Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Virginia Highways
- NOT THE POPULAR TYPE 1955 AUG 11
  Connie
- ARGENTINE BEEF 1955 AUG 19
  Freedom - loving people in Argentina Peron
- SPEAKER'S PLATFORM 1955 AUG 22
  2730 GI's who died in Korean United States Prisoners of Warprison camps
- BOTTLED UP 1955 AUG 26
  United States Milk Commission 's decision to retain controls
- ANOTHER HURRICANE'S COMING 1955 AUG 29
  Truman, Harry 's plan to tear into Political Parties Republican (GOP)
- HEY, FELLAS...! 1955 AUG 30
  Arabs Israel Dulles, John F. settlement proposal
- HE WON'T BOTHER YOU ANY MORE 1955 AUG 31
  free competition milk producer United States Milk Commission
- THE SPIRIT OF '56 1955 SEP 01
  budget should be balanced Political Parties Republican (GOP) Humphrey, Hubert H. Byrd, Harry F., Sr.
- 13- 14- 15- 16- 1955 SEP 06
  Virginia 's Labor Day toll Highways
- THE FALL'S FIRST READING LESSON 1955 SEP 07
  Stop Schools Crossing
- MAKING HAY WHILE THE SUN SHINES 1955 SEP 08
  '56 politics farmers discontent
- THAT'S WHAT I LIKE ABOUT THIS JOB- VARIETY 1955 SEP 09
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. Adenauer signs painted
- I HAVEN'T ANYTHING TO PACK 1955 SEP 13
  results for Germany Adenauer
- ONE MAN BAND 1955 SEP 15
  Economy business boom '56 hopes
- EASY STREET 1955 SEP 19
  penny-ante court fines taxes dodger
- MAN AND SUPERMAN 1955 SEP 20
  the power of Nature
- UM-UM-GOOD 1955 SEP 23
  State Fair Virginia
- THE CHIEF PILLAR 1955 SEP 24
  Constitutional interpretation John Marshall United States Supreme Court Constitution
- THE NEW PYRAMID 1955 SEP 30
  Communists (Reds) arms for Egypt
- AUTUMN LEAVES 1955 OCT 07
  '55 Tobacco Festival Richmond, Virginia
- LIKE FATHER-LIKE SON 1955 OCT 10
  increasing demands for federal Budget state funds
- THE QUEEN TURNED CRIMSON WITH FURY... 1955 OCT 14
  Russia Iran
- I GOT IT! 1955 OCT 18
  credit for a taxes cut Political parties Republican (GOP) Political parties Democrats (Dems)ocrats
- POP! 1955 OCT 25
  Saar defeat of "union" idea European Union EDC Big 3
- REBEL YELL 1955 OCT 28
  Lausche Stevenson, Adlai E., Harriman, Estes Georgia A Political parties Democrats (Dems)ocrats
- LOOKING AT NEXT YEAR'S MODEL 1955 NOV 05
  no new taxes Gov. Stanley 's budget
- FALL CLEANING 1955 NOV 10
  clean sweep Richmond, Virginia Henrico County, Virginia
- GENEVA SPIRIT 1955 NOV 11
  Geneva Going Going Gone!
- BETTER BAGGAGE 1955 NOV 12
  Molotov "nyets" Communists (Reds) dominance in Germany
- AT THE WHEEL 1955 NOV 16
  Principle of local self-govt. Gray Commission
- JUST LIKE THE REHEARSAL 1955 NOV 16
  applause I'm gonna run statement Stevenson, Adlai E. elections
- THE ROAD TO NOWHERE 1955 NOV 17
  Geneva
- THE THUMB ON THE SCALES 1955 NOV 21
  arms balance Israel Arabs
- CHICKEN LITTLE 1955 NOV 22
  the sky is falling! Stevenson, Adlai E. Political parties Republican (GOP) foreign policy
- PILGRIM'S PROGRESS 1955 NOV 24
  Stevenson, Adlai E. Estes Ave Johnson
- THE TRANSCENDENT ISSUE 1955 NOV 30
  United States Supreme Court United States Constitution Article V 10th amend
- TEARING DOWN THE GOALPOSTS 1955 DEC 01
  commercialized football W Robertson, A. Willis
- WELL AT LEAST THEY'LL AGREE... [1955]
  increase salary Eisenhower, Dwight D. '55 program
- HAVEN'T I SEEN YOU SOMEWHERE BEFORE? [1955]
  1901: trusts Labor unions American Federation of Labor (AFL)-Labor unions Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) merger
- PERSPECTIVE 1956 NOV 05
  Vote! America elections (from Pittsburg Press)
- WRITTEN IN BLOOD [1956]
  History Gallantry Hungary
- MULE TRAIN [1956]
  proposed taxes cuts 56 politics budget
- NOT THE ONLY THING THAT'S RED! [1956]
  Political parties Republican (GOP) deficits red ink predictions- 1956
- CALM ON THE SURFACE, BUT [1956]
  84th Congress '56 political undercurrent
- TRYING TO BEAT HIM OUT! [1956]
  Votes Eisenhower, Dwight D.'s proposed 1956 taxes cut
- YA KNOW, I FEEL BETTER, TOO! [1956]
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. improves elections campaign '56 blues
- HOLDING ON FOR DEAR LIFE [1956]
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. availability '56 politicians elections
- HORN OF PLENTY 1957 NOV 28
  Freedom of speech from want of press
- A BIG ROCK IN LITTLE ROCK [1957]
  Integration Civil Rights desegregation opposition Little Rock, Arkansas
- THE RAIL SPLITTER 1958 FEB 12
  Lincoln, Abraham courage honesty individual rights
- EXAMINATION TIME 1958 MAY 15
  School of Hard Knocks South American policy
- BIRD WATCHERS 1958 JUN 03
  De Gaulle North Atalntic Treaty Organization (NATO) France United States
- A FIRE CRACKER THAT NEEDS LIGHTING 1958 JUL 03
  deeper appreciation of freedom
- THE BIG TOP 1958 JUL 13
  Goldfine circus John Q
- I CAN HOLD A LOT MORE 1958 JUL 30
  Nasser Iraq Syria troubled waters Mideast
- A RINGER 1958 AUG 14
  United Nations Eisenhower, Dwight D.'s six-point peace plan
- WHAT AM I OFFERED? 1958 AUG
  United States helicopter crew Communists (Reds)s East Germany
- I'M GETTING TIRED OF THIS! 1958 AUG
  labor wages increases prices increases
- FEELING THE PINCH 1958 SEP 04
  Formosa China strait jacket Sam United States
- LONG RANGE SHELLS 1958 SEP 18
  Red China 's shelling of Quemoy United Nations chances
- SOMETHING BREWING? 1958 SEP 21
  Quemoy deal rumors Red China
- THAR'S GOLD IN THEM THAR HILLS! 1958 OCT 01
  Mt. Average citizen Political parties Republican (GOP) Political Parties Democrats (Dems)s
- YOU CAN BET THERE'S A STRING ATTACHED! 1958 OCT 08
  Ceasefire China Quemoy
- GOING FROM FLOWER TO FLOWER 1958 OCT 28
  stinger for the Political Parties Democrats (Dems)ocrats Eisenhower, Dwight D.
- JACK AND THE BEANSTALK 1958 OCT 30
  The climbing "All Time High" United States Debt
- THE MELANCHOLY DAYS 1958 NOV 07
  barren prospects fallen Congressional power
- GIVING US A BLACK EYE 1958 NOV 12
  schools bombings desegregation
- USING A NEW MIKE 1958 NOV 13
  On the air Communists (Reds) cold war Berlin Quemoy Mideast
- SANTA CLAUS IS COMING TO TOWN 1958 DEC 19
  taxpayer dollars Liberal give-away taxes budget
- SOMETHING TO KEEP IN MIND [1958]
  let's have more math science chem schools
- ANOTHER LAUNCHING NEEDED [1958]
  a push-the-pencil-education our schools
- SPOILING THE UNION [1958]
  Labor Day corruption in some unionsLabor unions
- UNDER TWO FLAGS [1958]
  "Buy!" [United States] White House
- SITTING UP WITH JUNIOR 1958
  ailing economy Sam United States
- FRAMED 1959 JAN 06
  below-zero temperatures
- AN' I'VE GOT TO PITCH TO HIM 1959 JAN 11
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. budget huge spending program economy
- TEN GALLON HAT 1959 JAN 14
  Lyndon Johnson 's filibuster victory Congress Johnson, Lyndon B.
- IT'S HARD TO SEE WHAT'S GOING ON FROM DOWN HERE! 1959 FEB 01
  Russian United States
- POSTSCRIPT 1959 FEB 06
  Dear Eisenhower, please come to Russia, Krushy, Dwight D. Khruschev, Nikita
- WATCH OUT THERE! 1959 FEB 10
  higher wages jumps priced out of business economy trade
- A NEW BIRTH OF FREEDOM 1959 FEB 12
  Abe Lincoln born 150 years ago today Lincoln, Abraham freedom
- NEEDED- ANOTHER GEORGE WASHINGTON 1959 FEB 22
  expanding fed. govt. indiv. Washington, George
- SUN SPOTS 1959 MAR 04
  Pioneer IV satellites
- MARCH WIND 1959 MAR 08
  Cold War hurricane Berlin Mideast
- A LOOK AT SOME OF THE TYPICAL WITNESSES...BEFORE THE RACKETS COMM 1959 MAR 09
  United states Rackets Committee
- THE TWO-A-YEAR BRAND 1959 MAR 25
  France United States Britain Summit Conference pill
- CORNERED! 1959 APR 15
  form 1040 Income Taxes Return
- AND TO THINK I CAUSED ALL THAT 1959 APR 30
  Luce - Morse uproar
- LONG MAY IT WAVE 1959 MAY 19
  a free voting primary elections Pennsylvania
- I WANT YOU TO MEET AN OLD FRIEND VETO 1959 MAY 31
  Veto Eisenhower, Dwight D. Congress
- QUICK, DOCTORS-I'M DYING! 1959 JUN 25
  Steel Labor unions expiring 3-yr contract
- AW COME ON FELLAS, BREAK IT UP! 1959 JUL 01
  continuing labor unions labor- steel fight
- THE THINKER 1959 JUL 15
  Strike - see Labor unions Labor unions [ steel striker]
- WHAT HAPPENED? 1959 SEP 09
  United Nations Russia n veto Laos United Nations investigating committee
- ONE MAN BAND 1959 SEP 22
  Blowing hot and cold same old Khrushchev, Nikita S.
- THE STRONG MEN GET TOGETHER 1959 SEP 24
  Our industrial muscle
- REACHING THE BOILING POINT 1959 SEP 30
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. steel strike heat
- I MIGHT HAVE TO USE SOME STEEL MYSELF! 1959 OCT 02
  Taft-Hartley Act Strike Steel Eisenhower, Dwight D.
- BLACK CLOUD 1959 OCT 22
  half-billion dollar loss in Pennsylvania closed by strike Steel
- TV GHOSTS 1959 NOV 06
  quiz lying they'll haunt me for a long time Television frauds
- IMPRESSIVE SKYLINE 1959 NOV 08
  best-protected area polio Pittsburgh, PA
- DARING YOUNG MAN ON THE FLYING TRAPEZE [1959]
  New Congress 60
- GETTING HIGHER ALL THE TIME! [1959]
  Estimated $11 billion deficits -1959 Budget
- SPACE HELMET No Date
  $74 billion space exploration budget
- WHY GRANDMA, WHAT BIG TEETH YOU HAVE! No Date
  Tax Bite Little... Red Taxes
- PGH No Date
  Stassen Was Here ( Pittsburgh, PA )
- REMINDER TO CARELESS DRIVERS No Date
  Highways Safety Icy roads
- I UNDERSTAND IT RUNS ON MONEY! No Date
  Space-age budget John Q
- ONLY A PROP No Date
  Billion dollar schools aid Budget Need to improve quality
- SIGNS OF THE TIMES No Date
  Out! Leave Quietly Bulganin
- OK, CUT ON THE POWER! No Date
  space exploration pioneering research program
- ANCHORS AWEIGH!! No Date
  Vanguard rocket Space exploration Double jinx Cape Canaveral, FL
- OH SAY CAN YOU SEE! No Date
  Satellite Sputnik #2 Satellites Explorer Space exploration
- BEHIND THE EIGHT BALL No Date
  The admin. Political Parties Democrats (Dems) ocratic 85th congress
- SHAPE OF THINGS TO COME No Date
  Mi$$le-heavy budget
- YOU CAN'T WIN No Date
  Before Taft-Hartley Act Do something- Eisenhower, Dwight D. after...
- STAIRWAY TO THE STARS No Date
  A more intensive education United States children schools
- A WORD FROM HUMPTY DUMPTY No Date
  Wall of opposition in Pennsylvania A Stassen
- VETERAN'S DAY SACRILEGE No Date
  40,070 Americans killed on highways Safety
- STIRRING UP THE HORNETS No Date
  South America n Unrest Comm. agitators Communists (Reds) Subversion
- JUST FILE IT WITH THE OTHERS No Date
  United Nations Peace Declaration San Francisco, CA
- CRYSTAL BALL No Date
  The West Communists (Reds)'s Party Boss Khrushchev, Nikita S. chev Russia
- HONK-HONK No Date
  Sports Baseball season Sports Football season
- LINE FORMS TO THE LEFT No Date
  Statehood application Panama Canal Zone Guam
- TERMITES IN THE NEW HOUSE No Date
  Free Austria Communists (Reds) Subversion
- THE 2-1 2 MUSKETEERS No Date
  Rearmament in Germany United States Britain France
- AND EVERYWHERE THAT MARY WENT No Date
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. '56 rumors Elections
- HIS DRAWING CARD No Date
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. Elections
- SAY, MR, ARE YOU PLANNING TO RUN? No Date
  Stevenson, Adlai E. Chicago, IL 13 Mos
- FOX HOLE No Date
  Goldfine gift Charges by Boston financier Frauds Sherman Adams
- ANOTHER SUMMIT PROBLEM No Date
  Middle East North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) Nato France Defense Eisenhower, Dwight D.
- STILL IN ORBIT No Date
  High food prices United States
- BARGAINING POINT No Date
  Tito purges
- ANOTHER ACADEMY AWARD PERFORMANCE No Date
  For "halt the recession "
- ANOTHER SUN THAT NEVER SETS No Date
  Churchill, Sir Winston 's accomplishments
- PRIMARY SCHOOL No Date
  How to get elected Political Parties Democrats (Dems)ocrats Elections
- HELP! No Date
  Rising prices Fixed income family
- PROSECUTING ATTORNEY No Date
  Eisenhower, Dwight D.'s promises record budget Political parties Democrats (Dems)s
- EAST OF EDEN No Date
  Garden of A. Eden closed Nasser
- BLOOD ON THE MOON No Date
  Hungary
- STRIKE! No Date
  Suez Crisis World peace Western prestige Big 3 Alliance
- AN APPLE FOR THE TEACHER No Date
  Federal control Govt fund$ - $chool$ Schools Budget
- WONDER WHERE I'LL GO THIS SUMMER? No Date
  Traffic Deaths Pennsylvania Highways Safety
- THE WEARING OF THE GREEN No Date
  Federal Spending Budget Our dollars
- RINGING THE CHRISTMAS BELL No Date
  Christmas Seals Pittsburgh, PA
- NOW STAY AWAY FROM HIM No Date
  Eisenhower, Dwight D. John Q Inflation
- GOING UP TOGETHER No Date
  Cost of living United Steel Workers dues Labor unions Inflation
- ROUGH LANDING FIELD No Date
  United Nations Arabs Hostility riots Israel Gaza Strip
- LANDSLIDE No Date
  cut the budget protests congress Capitol hill
- WARY WARRIOR No Date
  Petitions for Mayoralty race Political Parties Republican (GOP)
- ANOTHER TWISTER No Date
  State Political Parties Republican (GOP) Harrisburg, PA Point Park cuts Leader Budget
- SEE - IT DIDN'T FALL No Date
  France French govt. Faure Political blocks
- WAIT UNTIL WE GET THINGS CLEANED UP No Date
  Hungarian Communists (Reds)s United Nations Hammarskjold, Dag
- SIAMESE TWINS No Date
  Present overextended budget Demand of bigger spend
- VITAMIN PILLS No Date
  Pennsylvania Political Parties Republican (GOP) Eisenhower, Dwight D.
- FIGURE SKATER No Date
  Inflation Danger Thin Ice United States Economy
- BENEFACTOR No Date
  Federal control Federal funds for schools Budget
- KEEPING HIM JUMPING No Date
  United Nations Israel - Arabs problem Asia crises
- THE DEFENSE RESTS No Date
  Mixed Schools? No Schools Prince Edward County, VA Segregation
- THE RED BADGE OF COURAGE No Date
  World-wide service Red Cross
- WHAT'RE THEY DOING OUT THERE? - STILL TALKING No Date
  juvenile homes
- THE TIME HAS COME-THE WALRUS SAID No Date
  air incident reparation offer
- CAUGHT IN THE DOOR No Date
  Ford Motor Company 's guaranteed annual wage Employment industries
- BYSTANDER No Date
  delay of West Germany rearmament
- AND IT STARTED WITH SUCH A BANG No Date
  London disarmament conference
- NOT MUCH COMING UP! No Date
  Disarmament garden
- MODERN DESIGN No Date
  steel wage increase steel price increase inflation
- FLAG STAND No Date
  Freedom of religion assembly speech Flag Day
- PRIMARY SCHOOL No Date
  Big test May 21st How to win votes Elections
- NOW WATCH THE BIRDIE! No Date
  Communists (Reds) disarmament talk military buildup
- AND THIS IS THE SUPREME COURT No Date
  Recent topsy-turvy decisions John Q United States Supreme Court
- LEFT OVER FROM THE FOURTH No Date
  Civil Rights fireworks
- SUN SPOTS No Date
  Syria Israel Suez Canal Hot Middle East
- ROCK OF AGES No Date
  The empty tomb Religion Easter
- EXPLOSIONS No Date
  Atomic bombs tests Fallout controversy
- FALLOUT No Date
  Hydrogen bomb issue Stevenson, Adlai E.
- KING OF THE WILD FRONTIER No Date
  Presidential aspirations TN Kefauver Tennessee Elections
- MAYBE THEY CAN HELP YOU TOO! No Date
  Virginia legislature Prince Edward County, VA Schools Segregation
- THE ROAD OF LIFE No Date
  He is risen Religion Easter
- AN ALL-TOO-FAMILIAR SITUATION No Date
  continuing wage increase and price increase Inflation
- NOW LET'S SEE WHAT YOU'VE LEARNED No Date
  world Life's real test Grad Schools Education
- WE'RE A BIG COUNTRY TOO! No Date
  industrial might- Pittsburgh, PA Kozlov
- HELP! No Date
  Approaching steel strikes John Q Labor unions
- ME AND MY SHADOW No Date
  Alaska: biggest state Smallest population
- SNOWED UNDER No Date
  anti-communist votes in West Berlin Communists (Reds)
- THE DAY AFTER THANKSGIVING No Date
  enjoyed the feast Political Parties Republican (GOP) Alaska results Elections
- TO PATCH THE WALL No Date
  North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) Sacrifice Hard Work
- FROM HERE TO ETERNITY No Date
  An "on the target" ICBM Ballistic missiles
- A SIGHT FOR SORE EYES No Date
  United States West's lag
- SIGNS OF THE TIMES No Date
  Our troubled world Satellites Sputnik go Home!
- MAKING HIMSELF COMFORTABLE No Date
  5th amendment Subversion ve & Hoodlum United States Constitution
- NEXT!! No Date
  Khrushchev, Nikita S.
- THE GOBIN'LL GET US IF WE DON'T WATCH OUT No Date
  Russian advances
- MOON OVER MANHATTAN No Date
  Turkish- Syrian dispute United Nations
- WISHING ON A STAR No Date
  Communists (Reds) sphere American Scientists satellites
- FOLLOWING CLOSE BEHIND No Date
  Soviet satellites Tough Communists (Reds) diplo. policy
- HEY, FOSTER, I'M GETTING SEASICK! No Date
  Ship of State Dulles, John F. Syria
- STILL ROWING No Date
  Stassen Communists (Reds) scuttled Disarmament talks
- HEY LOOK! I'M OUT IN FRONT! No Date
  United States Atom buildup Russian buildup Atomic bombs
- DIOGENES No Date